<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on Yuchu Luo - 罗宇矗</title>
    <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on Yuchu Luo - 罗宇矗</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Yuchu Luo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/machine-learning/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>An Quadrotor Safety Monitorting System</title>
      <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/an-quadrotor-safety-monitorting-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/an-quadrotor-safety-monitorting-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implemented and optimized a anomaly detection algorithm called Isolation Forest, which can receive temporal information and feed back the abnormal degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed an exploration tool for the iForest algorithm, which can do visualization to a certain extent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Won Provincial 1st Prizes both in the 2017 Challenge Cup and the E-Commerce Competition, Technical group. And get the qualification to the 2017 national contests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Rossmann Store Sales</title>
      <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/rossmann/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/rossmann/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rossmann operates over 3,000 drug stores in 7 European countries. Currently, Rossmann store managers are tasked with predicting their daily sales for up to six weeks in advance. Store sales are influenced by many factors, including promotions, competition, school and state holidays, seasonality, and locality. With thousands of individual managers predicting sales based on their unique circumstances, the accuracy of results can be quite varied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In their first Kaggle competition, Rossmann is challenging you to predict 6 weeks of daily sales for 1,115 stores located across Germany. Reliable sales forecasts enable store managers to create effective staff schedules that increase productivity and motivation. By helping Rossmann create a robust prediction model, you will help store managers stay focused on what’s most important to them: their customers and their teams!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(There are a lot of flaws due to lack of time.)
You can see the report &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wolegechu/Machine_Learning_Nanodegree/tree/master/Capstone&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Customer Segments</title>
      <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/customer-segments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/customer-segments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project I applied unsupervised learning techniques on product spending data collected for customers of a wholesale distributor in Lisbon, Portugal to identify customer segments hidden in the data. I first explored the data by selecting a small subset to sample and determine if any product categories highly correlate with one another. Afterwards, I preprocessed the data by scaling each product category and then identifying (and removing) unwanted outliers. With the good, clean customer spending data, I applied PCA transformations to the data and implement clustering algorithms to segment the transformed customer data. Finally, I compared the segmentation found with an additional labeling and consider ways this information could assist the wholesale distributor with future service changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The main techniques used:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clustering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More Clustering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feature Scaling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feature Selection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PCA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feature Transformation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the code(iPython notebook) &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wolegechu/Machine_Learning_Nanodegree/blob/master/3.%20Customer%20Segments/customer_segments.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Donors for CharityML</title>
      <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/finding-donors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/finding-donors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, I applied supervised learning techniques and an analytical mind on data collected for the U.S. census to help CharityML (a fictitious charity organization) identify people most likely to donate to their cause. I first explored the data to learn how the census data is recorded. Next, I applied a series of transformations and preprocessing techniques to manipulate the data into a workable format. Then I evaluated several supervised learners of my choice on the data, and considered which is best suited for the solution. Afterwards, I optimized the model I had selected and presented it as my solution to CharityML. Finally, I explored the chosen model and its predictions under the hood, to see just how well it&amp;rsquo;s performing when considering the data it&amp;rsquo;s given. predicted selling price to the statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The main techniques used:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decision Trees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regression &amp;amp; Classification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regressions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kernel Methods &amp;amp; SVM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GaussianNB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensemble learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RandomForestClassifier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the code(iPython notebook) &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wolegechu/Machine_Learning_Nanodegree/blob/master/2.%20Finding%20Donors/finding_donors.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Boston Housing Prices</title>
      <link>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/boston-housing-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luoyuchu.com/project/boston-housing-prices/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, I applied basic machine learning concepts on data collected for housing prices in the Boston, Massachusetts area to predict the selling price of a new home. I first explored the data to obtain important features and descriptive statistics about the dataset. Next, I properly split the data into testing and training subsets, and determine a suitable performance metric for this problem. Then I analyzed performance graphs for a learning algorithm with varying parameters and training set sizes. This enabled me to pick the optimal model that best generalizes for unseen data. Finally, I tested this optimal model on a new sample and compare the predicted selling price to my statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The main techniques used:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluating Model performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Model Evaluation &amp;amp; Validation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Model Optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the code(iPython notebook) &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wolegechu/Machine_Learning_Nanodegree/blob/master/1.%20Boston%20Housing%20Prices/boston_housing.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
